# **Bryan Hankins**

## Freelance Front End Developer

Address Evansville, IN, 47712

**Phone** 8125491887

E-mail masterpokemo@gmail.com

**WWW** https://bryanhankins.github.io/

**LinkedIn** https://www.linkedin.com/in/bryan-

hankins-8668811a

Front end developer with business experience in leading and doing with multiple projects developed. With a foundational grasp of various CSS and HTML options, plugins, development platforms and security requirements according to up-to-date standards. Data-driven individual with excellent grasp of Google Analytics and other search optimization needs.

#### **Skills**

Front End Web Development

HTML5 & CSS & JavaScript

Angular

React

12djs

Webpack

Babel

NPM

**AJAX** 

**JSON** 

Bootstrap

**LESS** 

Sass

Restful APis

Git

# **Work History**

2020-11 - 2021-09

**CEO of Company** 

Ffff Web Design, Dsafsf, IN

- Increased company revenue by tens of thousands in profit in 6 months through aggressive new market strategies.
- Created multiple under NDA projects for companies from Entertainment Industry to Food Service Industry and to Local Clubs.
- Managed partnerships and strategic business relationships by negotiating contract terms and handling conflicts.
- Developed key operational initiatives to drive and maintain substantial business growth.

#### 2021-03 - 2021-05

## Freelance Web Designer

Ivy Tech Community College, Evansville, IN

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Used Angular Mean , HTML , CSS , Javascript, Bootstrap , rest API AJAX, JSON and GIT
- Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.

### **Education**

2020-11 - 2021-05

#### **Certification: Web Foundations**

Ivy Tech Community College - Evansville Indiana

- Member of Honors Society USA
- Professional development completed in Web Foundations

## **Projects**

#### Multiple NDA PROJECTS.

- Created over 20 web applications under NDA for companies from the food to entertainment industry. From the well known to the obscure.
- In some of my NDA Projects I have used technologies like HTML5, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, Node.js Typescript, WebPack, Babel, NPM, AJAX and JSON, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub. Docker and MongoDB
- Translated Websites made from Websites like Wix.com . To a proper fully controlled mobile friendly website.
- Facilitated meetings between clients to emphasis the pros of a proper website with also an opportunity to help expand their business.
- Produced Quality Web Applications so frequently that my clients bring me more clients.